>> pip install pandas numpy
>>pip install pandas numpy yfinance

>>New Functions:

    calculate_rsi: Computes the Relative Strength Index (RSI).
    calculate_profit_margin: Computes the profit margin from the income statement.
    calculate_eps: Computes the Earnings Per Share (EPS) from the income statement.

Fetching Financial Data:

    income_statement is fetched using yfinance for calculating profit margin and EPS.
    Shares outstanding are fetched from the stock info.

Menu Options:

    Added options for RSI, Profit Margin, and EPS calculations.
